Macbeth Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, ca. 1880-ca. 1968, Series 8:; (Box 135-161; 12.1 linear feet)
  - Photographs of Artwork and Records of Paintings Sold, ca. 1900-1952, 8.3:
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Artwork (NMc79), n.d. (Box 161 (hol))
Jan. 30-Feb. 19, 1934 Paintings and Drawings by Lintott (NMc3:699-700)
Feb. 20-Mar. 12, 1933 Paintings by C. K. Chatterton (N442:69-70; Br15:63-64; NMc3:703-704)
Feb. 27-Mar. 12, 1934 Golinkin (Br15:51-52; NMc3:707-708)
Mar. 6-20, 1933 Drawings by Meyer Bernstein (NMc3:709)
Mar. 13-36, 1934 Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3:710)
Mar. 20-Apr. 2, 1934 Watercolors of South America by Eliot O'Hara (Br15:65-67; NMc3:712)
Mar. 27-Apr. 16, 1934 Memorial Exhibition, Paintings by Charles H. Davis, 1856-1933 (Br15:68-75; NMc3:715-722)
Apr. 3-16, 1933 Drawings by Hetty Beatty, Sculptor (NMc3:726)
Apr. 10-23, 1934 Oils and Watercolors by Gertrude Schweitzer (NMc3:726)
Apr. 17-May 1, 1934 Monhegan Marines by Jan Connaway (Br15:76; NMc3:727)
May 1-14, 1934 Watercolors and Pastels by H. Amaird Oberteuffer and Karl Oberteuffer (NMc3:728)
May 1-21, 1934 Review of the Season (NMc3:729)
May 7-14, 1934 Paintings by John C. E. Taylor, William Luther King, Stuyvesant van Veen (NMc3:730)
May 1934? Third Exhibition and Sale of American Paintings at $100 (NMc3:731)
June 4-15, 1934 Our Glorious Navy: Paintings by Arthur Beaumont, Lieut. U.S.N.R. (NMc3:732-733)
Oct. 1-15, 1934 Opening Exhibition, Season of 1934-1935, Paintings by Nelson A. Moore, 1924-1902 (NMc3:735-736)
Oct. 16-30, 1934 Collectors Examples of American Painting (NMc3:739-740)
Nov. 7-19, 1934 Greenland and Other Subjects by Rockwell Kent (NMc3:742-743)
Nov. 20-Dec. 3, 1934 Southern New Mexico: Drawings and Lithographs by Peter Hurd (NMc3:748-749)
Nov. 20-Dec. 11, 1934 Brackman (N224:71-72; Br15:77-78; NMc3:742-743)
Dec. 4-31, 1934 Lithographs and Drawings of Stow Wengenroth (NMc3:750)
Dec. 11-31, 1934 Robert Hallowell, Mostly Portraits (NMc3:751-752)
Jan. 2-14, 1935 Leopold Seyffert, Subjects from Guatemala and Flowers (NMc3:754-755)
Jan. 22-Feb. 4, 1935 Group of Paintings by Younger Artists (NMc3:756)
Feb. 5-19, 1935 Robert Strong Woodward, "Landscapes of New England" (Br15:79-80/NMc4:401-402)
Feb. 19-28, 1935 Portraits by Leonebel Jacobs (Br15:81-83; N442:73; NMc4:404)
Mar. 5-18, 1935 Loan Exhibition (NMc4:408-409)
Apr. 10-30, 1935 St. Ives by Hayley Lever (NMc3:761-762)
Apr. 23-May 13, 1935 Still Lifes by Emil Carlsen, 1853-1932 (Br15:84-85; 3092:327-238; NMc4:411-413)
May 14-June 3, 1935 Watercolors and Pastels (NMc4:414)
Summer 1935 Summer Exhibition (NMc4:415)
Oct. 13-26, 1935 American Masters Loaned for Exhibition (N441:1185-1187)
Oct. 8-21, 1935 Recent Paintings by Frederick C. Frieseke (Br15:86-86; NMc4:416-417)
Nov. 19-Dec. 3, 1935 Drawings by Lintott (Br15:88-89; NMc4:418-419)
Dec. 3-31, 1935 Drawings and Lithographs by Stow Wengenroth (NMc4:420)
Dec. 9-31, 1935 Oils, Watercolors, Drawings by Gertude Schweitzer (NMc4:421)
Jan. 14-Feb. 3, 1936 Herbert Meyer (Br15:92-93; NMc4:422-423)
Feb. 1936 Group Exhibition (NMc4:429)
Feb. 1936 Drawings by Eastman Johnson (NMc4:430)
Feb. 4-17, 1936 Homer D. Martin, 1836-1897, Centennial Exhibition (N442:74-75; Br 15:94-95; NMc4:426-427)
Mar. 10-23, 1936 Contemporary Americans
Mar. 10-23, 1936 Watercolors by Steven Donahos (NMc4:430)
Mar. 24-Apr. 16, 1936 Brackman (Br15:96-98; NMc4:431)
Apr. 7-27, 1936 Paintings and Watercolors by C. K. Chatterton (Br15:99; NMc4:433-434)
Apr. 28-May 11, 1936 Group Exhibition (NMc4:435)
Apr. 28-May 11, 1936 Watercolors by Mary S. Powers (NMc4:435)
May 19-June 1, 1936 Drawings by Richard Guggenheimer (NMc4:436)
May 27-June 3, 1936 Pastel Portraits by Frank Root McCreery (NMc4:437-438)
Oct. 5-26, 1936 Opening Exhibition, 45th Season, New Paintings by Fourteen American Painters (Br15:100-101; NMc4:447-448)
Nov. 4-16 1936 Paintings by Elliot Orr (Br15:102-103; D23:1213-1214; NMc4:444-445)
Nov. 17-30, 1936 Recent Paintings by Ogden M. Pleissner (Br15:104-105; NMc4:447-448)
Dec. 1936 Lester D. Boronda: Paintings from Mason's Island (NMc4:449)
Dec. 15, 1936-Jan. 18, 1937 An Introduction to Homer (N43:37-45; D36:969-978; N442:80-88; NMc4:451-460)
Jan. 19-Feb. 1, 1937 Portraits (N442:76-77; NMc4:478-479
Jan. 19-Feb. 1, 1937 Group of Watercolors (NMc4:480)
Feb. 2-15, 1937 John C. E. Taylor: Flower Arrangements and Other Oils (NMc4:481)
Feb. 16-Mar. 1, 1937 Paintings and Watercolors by Horace Day (Br15:106-108; NMc4:482)
Mar. 2-15, 1937 Hayley Lever, Paintings New and Old (Br15:109: NMc4:485)
Mar. 2-15, 1937 Paintings by Josef Presser (NM4:485)
Mar. 16-Apr. 5, 1937 Recent Work by Jon Corbino (Br15:110)
Apr. 13-26, 1937 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings, Crayon Drawings and Dry Points by the late Alexander Shilling (NMc4:499)
Apr. 30-May 17, 1937 Edna Reindel (Br15:111-112;NMc4:503)
Oct. 5-19, 1937 American Paintings Dedicating the Art Gallery Woman's Club Art Building, Montana State University (NMc4:505-514)
Oct. 6-18, 1937 Opening Exhibition, Paintings by a Group of Contemporary Artists (NMc4:517)
Oct. 19-Nov. 1, 1937 First Exhibition, Watercolors by Andrew Wyeth (Br15:113-114; NMc4:518-519)
Nov. 2-15, 1937 Marine and Other Subjects from the Canary Islands by Cadwallader Washburn (Br15:115-116; NMc4:524-525)
Nov. 16-29, 1937 Paintings by Lorenzo James Hatch (Br15: 117-118; N442:78-79; NMc4:524-525)
Nov. 30-Dec. 14, 1937 Monhegan Island, Maine, Marines by Jay Connaway (NMc4:527)
Jan. 4-17, 1938 "The Eight" Thirty Years Later (NMc4:529-530)
Jan. 18-Feb. 1, 1938 Paintings by Dale Nichols (NMc4:538-540)
Feb. 8-21, 1938 Vermont in Watercolors by Stanford Stevens (NMc4:541-542)
Feb. 8-21, 1938 Modern American Interior: Prizewinning Design and Selected Drawings from a Competition Sponsored by James H. Blauvet and Associates, Interior Designers (NMc4:543)
Mar. 1-14, 1938 Paintings and Watercolors by Anne Goldthwaite (NMc4:546-547)
Mar. 8-21, 1938 Recent Watercolors of Woodstock, Charleston, New England by John W. Taylor (NMc4:548-549)
Mar. 22-Apr. 11, 1938 Jon Corbino (NMc4:554-561)
Apr. 12-25, 1938 Paintings by Ohio Artists (NMc4:580-571)
Apr. 26-May 9, 1938 Paintings by Furman Joseph Finck (NMc4:572-573)
May-June 1938 Winslow Homer: Watercolors and Early Oils from the Estate of Mrs. Charles S. Homer and Other Sources (NMc4:574-579)
Oct. 4-28, 1938 Opening Exhibition (NMc4:581)
Nov. 1-23, 1938 Dale Nichols, Watercolors and Tempera of Alaskan Subjects (Br15:122-124; NMc4:582-583)
Nov. 29-Dec. 19, 1938 Sea Island Country Watercolors by Horace Day (NMc4:584)
Jan. 10-30, 1939 Herbert Meyer (Br15:125-126; NMc5:588-589)
Feb. 7-27, 1939 American Watercolors Past and Present (Br 15:127-132; NMc4:592-597
Mar. 7-Apr. 3, 1939 Monhegan by Jay Connaway (Br15:133; NMc4:602-603)
Apr. 5-24, 1919 Oils and Watercolors by Ogden M. Pleissner (Br15:134; NMc4:606-607)
May 2-22, 1939 Paintings by Francis Chapin, Antonio P. Matino, and Moses Soyer and Drawings by Jon Corbino (D283:334-335; Br15:138; NMc4:609-611)
Oct. 10-30, 1939 Andrew Wyeth (Br15:139; NMc4:614)
Nov. 1-30, 1939 American Paintings, Watercolors, Prints, Drawings (Br15:140; NMc4:616-617)
Nov. 29-Dec. 19, 1939 Horace Day (Br15:120-121)
Dec. 5-30, 1939 In the Georges Islands, Maine: Paintings by N.C. Wyeth (Br15:141; NMc4:618)
Dec. 5-30, 1939 Dry Brush Drawings by Stow Wengenroth (NMc4:618-619)
Jan. 2-27, 1940 Brackman (NMc4:623-624)
Jan. 30-Feb. 19, 1940 Paintings by Moses Soyer (D238:337-339; D176:618-620; Br15:142; NMc4:630-631)
Feb. 20-Mar. 11, 1940 Watercolors by Emil J. Kosa, Jr. (Br15:143; NMc4:637)
Feb. 23-Mar. 7, 1938 Herbert Dickens Ryman (NMc4:546)
Mar. 12-30, 1940 Paintings by Edna Reindel (Br15:144-145; NMc4:436)
April 1940 Paintings and Drawings by Jon Corbino (Br15:146-147; NMc4:639-640)
May 7-18, 1940 "Star Boat Races," by Gerald Foster (NMc4:640)
Summer 1940 Summer Exhibition
Oct. 1940 October Exhibition (NMc4:642)
Nov. 12-Dec. 2, 1940 Paintings by Antonio P. Martino (Br15:150-151; NMc4:645)
Dec. 10-30, 1940 Monhegan Paintings and Sketches by Jay Connaway (Br15:148-149; NMc4:648)
Dec. 31, 1940-Jan. 13, 1941 Oils and Watercolors by Contemporary Artists (NMc4:649)
Jan. 14-Feb. 3, 1941 Paintings and Drawings by Augustus Vincent Tack (Br15:152-154; NMc4:650-651)
Feb. 4-24, 1941 Recent Paintings by Peter Hurd (NMc4:652)
Feb. 18-Mar. 3, 1941 Earl Gross Watercolors (NHS4:434-435; NMc4:654-655)
Feb. 25-Mar. 16, 1941 Recent Paintings by Herman Maril (Br15:155-157; NMc4:656-657)
Mar. 18-Apr. 5, 1941 Joseph de Martini Gouache Paintings (Br15:158-159; NMc4:656)
Mar. 25-Apr. 7, 1941 Men of Moment: Drawings by Ivan Opffer (NMc4:660)
Apr. 8-28, 1941 Paintings by Orland Campbell (Br15:160-161; NMc4:661-662)
Apr. 29-May 12, 1941 Small Paintings by Moses Soyer (Br15:162-163; D283:340-341; NMc4:667-668)
May 1941 Group Exhibition (NMc4:667)
May 13-24, 1941 The 1941 Showing of Blauvelt Interiors (NMc4:669-671)
May-June 1941 Group Exhibition (NMc4:669)
Sept. 1941 Group Exhibition: Oils (NMc4:682)
Oct. 7-27, 1941 Third Exhibition of Watercolors by Andrew Wyeth (Br15:164-165; NMc4:685)
Oct. 28-Nov. 17, 1941 Recent Oils and Watercolors by Ogden M. Pleissner (Br15:166-167; NMc4:685-686)
Oct. 28-Nov. 17, 1941 Watercolors by Merrill A. Bailey (NMc4:685)
Nov. 18-Dec. 1, 1941 Drawings and Watercolors by Carl Newland Werntz (Br15:168-170; NMc4:688-689)
Nov. 18-Dec. 1, 1941 Hymn to the Sun: A Sculpture in Bronze by Emily Winthrop Miles
Dec. 1941 Group Exhibition (NMc4:690)
Dec. 2-22, 1941 Original Dolls by Edith Flack Ackley and their Portraits in Watercolor by Telka Ackley (NMc4:690)
Jan. 5-24, 1942 Paintings by Furman Joseph Finck (NMc4:694)
Jan. 5-24, 1942 Watercolors of Maine and Florida by Maurice Becker (NMc4:694-695)
Jan. 19-Feb. 14, 1942 Watercolors, Pastels, Drawings by Jerome Myers, 1867-1940 (NMc4:696)
Feb. 16-28, 1942 Watercolors by Cory Kilvert (Br15:173-174; NMc4:697-698)
Feb. 16-Mar. 7, 1942 Paintings by Deceased American Masters (Br15:171-172; NMc4:697-698)
Mar. 9-28, 1942 Paintings by Marsden Hartley (Br15:175-176; NMc4:700-701)
Mar. 9-28, 1942 Watercolors by Karl Mattern (Br15:177-178; NMc4:700)
Apr. 13-30, 1942 Fiftieth Anniversary Exhibition, 1892-1942 (3092:344-347; NMc4:703-704)
May 4-29, 1942 Group Exhibition (NMc4:707)
June 1942 June Exhibition (NMc4:708)
June 15-27, 1942 War Bond Exhibitions of Contemporary American Art (NMc4:708)
Sept. 1942 September Exhibition (NMc4:709)
Nov. 16-28, 1942 Watercolors by Jean Paul Slusser (Br15:179-180; NMc4:710)
Nov. 24-Dec. 12, 1942 T. Chambers, First American Modern (Br15:181-184; NMc4:711-714)
Dec. 1-14, 1942 Watercolors by Red Robin (Br15:208-210; NMc4:715-716)
Dec. 15, 1942-Jan. 2, 1943 Leaves From a Soldier's Sketchbook by Pvt. Olin Dows, U. S. Army (Br15:204; NMc4:717)
Jan. 4-23, 1943 Paintings by Sprinchorn (Br15:185; NMc4:717-718)
Feb. 1-13, 1943 Group Exhibition (NMc4:719)
Feb. 15-Mar. 6, 1943 Small Paintings by Moses Soyer (Br15:186; NMc4:720)
Mar. 15-27, 1943 Ellen du Pont Wheelwright (Br15:187-188; NMc4:721)
Mar. 15-27, 1943 Watercolors by Cory Kilvert (Br15:189; NMc4:721)
Mar. 29-Apr. 17, 1943 Recent Paintings by Joseph De Martini (Br15:190-191; NMc4:722)
Mar. 29-Apr. 17, 1943 Watercolor Exhibition (NMc4:722)
Apr. 19-May 1, 1943 Corp. Herman Maril (Br15:197; NMc4:728)
Apr. 19-May 8, 1943 Theodore Robinson (Br15:196; NMc4:723-725)
May-June 1943 Group Exhibition (NMc4:729)
Sept. 1943 Group Exhibition (NMc4:731)
Oct. 11-30, 1943 Watercolors by Henry Gasser (Br15:198-199; NMc4:723-733)
Nov. 1-20, 1943 Tempera and Watercolors by Andrew Wyeth (Br15:200-201; NMc4:735-736)
Nov. 22-Dec. 4, 1943 Portraits of Children by Barnard Lentott (NMc4:741-742)
Dec. 1943 Group Exhibition (NMc4:741)
Dec. 6-24, 1943 Rural Vermont: Watercolors by Sylvia Wright (Br15:202-203; NMc4:743-744)
Jan. 3-15, 1944 Watercolors of War by Red Robin (Br15:205-207NMc4:743-744)
Jan. 31-Feb. 19, 1944 Loan Exhibition, Worthington Whittredge, 1825-1910 (Br15:211-212; NMc4:745-746)
Feb. 21-Mar. 11, 1944 Paintings by Constance Richardson (NMc4:749-750)
Mar. 13-Apr. 1, 1944 Watercolors by Vanessa Helder (Br15:213; NMc4:751, 753)
Mar. 13-Apr. 1, 1944 Temperas and Watercolors by Peter Hurd (Br15:214-215; NMc4:751-753)
Apr. 3-22, 1944 American Paintings of the Early 19th Century (NMc4:754-755)
Apr. 24-May 13, 1944 Brackman (Br15:216-217; NMc4:756-757)
May 15-June 3, 1944 Two Vermont Artists: Clay Bartlett and Arthur K. D. Healy (Br15:218-220; NMc4:758-759)
June 5-24, 1944 Women at War by Edna Reindel (NMc4:760)
July 1944 Group Exhibition (NMc4:762)
Sept. 25-Oct. 15, 1944 Group Exhibition (NMc4:763)
Oct. 16-Nov. 4, 1944 Paintings by Felicia Meyer (NMc4:764-765)
Nov. 15-Dec. 2, 1944 The Aleutian Air Force: Paintings by Ogden M. Pleissner (NMc4:766-767)
Dec. 4-23, 1944 Paintings by John W. Taylor (Br15:221; NMc4:769-770)
Jan. 8-27, 1945 Paintings by Carl Gaertner (Br15:222-223; NMc4:771-772)
Jan. 29-Feb. 10, 1945 Contemporary American Watercolors (NMc4:772)
Feb. 19-Mar. 10, 1945 Paintings and Watercolors by Maurice Becker (NMc4:773-774)
Mar. 12-31, 1945 Some Early 19th Century Americans (NMc4:777-778)
Apr. 2-21, 1945 Paintings by Joseph De Martini (Br14:194-195; NMc4:778-779)
Apr. 23-May 12, 1945 Gouaches by Herman Maril (Br15:224; NMc4:781)
Apr. 23-May 12, 1945 Paintings by Molly Luce (NMc4:781-782)
May-June 1945 Group Exhibition: Contemporary Oils and Watercolors (NMc4:783)
July, Sept., 1945 Group Exhibition (NMc4:783)
Oct. 1-7, 1945 Group Exhibition (NMc4:784)
Oct. 26-Nov. 17, 1945 Tempera and Watercolors by Andrew Wyeth (Br15:225-226; NMc:787-788)
Nov. 26-Dec. 15, 1945 Marsden Hartley: Paintings and Drawings (Br15:227-228; NMc4:791-792)
Dec. 1945 Christmas Exhibition (NMc4:793)
Jan. 7-26, 1946 New York in Watercolors by James Lechay (NMc4:794)
Jan. 28-Feb. 16, 1946 Herbert Meyer (NMc4:795)
Feb. 18-Mar. 19, 1946 Ary Stillman (NMc4:797-798)
Mar. 11-30, 1946 Watercolors by Arthur K. D. Haley (NMc4:800-801)
Apr. 1-20, 1946 Albert P. Ryder (3092:314-316; NMc4:802-805)
Apr. 22-May 11, 1946 Paintings by Constance Richardson (NMc4:809-810)
May 13-31, 1946 Furman Jospeh Finck (NMc4:811-812)
June 1946 Group Exhibition (NMc4:813)
Sept. 1946 Group Exhibition (NMc4:814)
Sept. 30-Oct. 19, 1946 Gouaches by Charles Schucker (NMc4:815)
Oct. 2-Nov. 9, 1946 Watercolors and Drawings by Olin Dows (NMc4:816-817)
Nov. 4-30, 1946 Ogden M. Pleissner (NMc4:818)
Dec. 2-28, 1946 Oils and Watercolors by Emil J. Kosa, Jr. (NMc4:819-820)
Jan. 6-26, 1947 Carl Gaertner (NMc4:821-822)
Jan. 27-Feb. 15, 1947 Carl Sprinchorn (NMc4:823)
Mar. 3-22, 1947 Dorothy Hoyt (NMc4:825-826)
Mar. 24-Apr. 12, 1947 Joseph De Martini (NMc4:827-828)
Apr. 14-May 10, 1947 Whistler Loan Exhibition (NMc4:828-834)
June-July, 1947 Summer Exhibition (NMc4:840)
Sept. 1947 Group Exhibition (NMc4:841)
Oct. 13-Nov. 1, 1947 Paintings by Allen Tucker (D57:205-207; NMc4:842-844)
Nov. 3-22, 1947 Watercolors by Henry Gasser (NMc4:846-847)
Nov. 24-Dec. 13, 1947 James Lechay (NMc4:849-850)
Dec. 15, 1947-Jan. 3, 1948 Watercolor Exhibition (NMc4:851)
Jan. 5-24, 1948 Clay Bartlett (NMc4:852-853)
Jan. 26-Feb. 14, 1948 Oils and Watercolors by Contemporary Artists (NMc4:854)
Feb. 16-Mar. 6, 1948 Herman Maril (NMc4:855-856)
Mar. 22-Apr. 3, 1948 American Art: A Multiple Exhibition arranged by the Associated Dealers in American Art (NMc4:857-858)
Apr. 5-24, 1948 Raphael Gleitsmann (NMc4:866-867)
Apr. 26-May 15, 1948 Oils and Watercolors by John La Farge (NMc4:864)
May-Sept. 1948 Group Exhibitions (NMc:867)
Oct. 4-23, 1948 Watercolors by Charles Culver (NMc4:869-870)
Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1948 Ogden M. Pleissner (NMc4:872)
Nov. 15-Dec. 4, 1948 Andrew Wyeth (NMc4:874-875)
Nov. 21-Dec. 4, 1948 Oils and Gouaches by Charles Schucker (D56:1062-1065; NMc4:332-333)
Dec. 6-31, 1948 Watercolors and Drawings by Hermann Gross (NMc4:877-878)
Jan. 4-22, 1949 Electra Bostwick (NMc4:879, 882)
Jan. 27-Feb. 19, 1949 Paintings by Edna Reindel (NMc4:880-881)
Feb. 28-Mar. 19, 1949 Thomas Doughty (NMc4:885-887)
Mar. 21-Apr. 9, 1949 Watercolors by Arthur K. D. Healy (NMc4:889)
Apr. 12-30, 1949 Drawings by Olin Dows (NMc4:890)
May 1949 Group Exhibition (NMc4:894)
Oct. 10-29, 1949 Clay Bartlett: Paintings of North and South America (NMc4:895-896)
Nov. 1-19, 1949 Watercolors by Henry Gasser (NMc4:897-898)
Nov. 21-Dec. 10, 1949 Oils and Gouaches by Charles Shucker (NMc4:332-333)
Dec. 1949 Watercolor Exhibition (NMc4:334)
Jan. 3-21, 1950 Carl Gaertner (NMc4:335-356)
Jan. 23-Feb. 11, 1950 Constance Richardson (NMc4:337-338)
Mar. 6-25, 1950 John Taylor (NMc4:339-340)
Apr. 1950 Joseph De Martini (NMc4:341)
May 8-27, 1950 Carl Sprinchorn (NMc4:342-343)
Summer 1950 Summer Exhibition (NMc4:345)
Oct. 9-28, 1950 Caseins by James Lechay (NMc4:345-346)
Oct. 31-Nov. 18, 1950 Ogden M. Pleissner: Paris and the Provinces (NMc4:347-348)
Nov. 21-Dec. 9, 1950 Andrew Wyeth (NMc4:349-350)
Jan. 2-20, 1951 Nat Koffman (NMc4:356-357)
Jan. 22-Feb. 10, 1951 Watercolors by Hermann Gross (NMc4:358)
Feb. 12-Mar. 3, 1951 Charles Culver: Watercolors (D55:390-391; NMc4:359)
Mar. 5-24, 1951 Paintings by Francis Colburn (NMc4:360)
Mar. 27-Apr. 14, 1951 Paintings by Herman Maril (D56:461; NMc4:361)
Apr. 16-May 5, 1951 Raphael Gleitsmann (NMc4:362-363)
Summer 1951 Summer Exhibition (NMc4:364)
July 7-Aug. 4, 1951 Paintings and Drawings by Andrew Wyeth (NMc4:364-381)
Nov. 26-Dec. 15, 1951 Watercolors by Arthur K. D. Healy (NMc4:387)
Feb. 4-Mar. 1, 1952 Italian Landscapes by George Inness (NMc4:388-389)
Apr. 1952 1892: Sixtieth Anniversary Exhibition (3092:348-350)
June-July, Sept. 1952 Summer Exhibition (NMc4:392)
Nov. 6-29, 1952 Andrew Wyeth (NMc4:391-392)